{
    "subject": "resource/Max_Eckert-Greifendorff",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Chemnitz",
    "human_readable": "Max Eckert-Greifendorff was born in Chemnitz.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9210327863693237,
            "question": "Where was Max Eckert-Greifendorff born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.89128577709198,
            "question": "What year was Max Eckert-Greifendorff born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7902607917785645,
            "question": "What is the significance of Chemnitz in relation to Max Eckert-Greifendorff's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7597209811210632,
            "question": "What is Max Eckert-Greifendorff known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6579273343086243,
            "question": "Was Max Eckert-Greifendorff involved in any significant events?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6408290863037109,
            "question": "Where might we find more information about Max Eckert-Greifendorff?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6368077993392944,
            "question": "Is there any information about Max Eckert-Greifendorff's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.536395788192749,
            "question": "Do we know anything about Max Eckert-Greifendorff's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.517528772354126,
            "question": "Did Max Eckert-Greifendorff have any notable accomplishments?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.429017573595047,
            "question": "Are there any connections between Max Eckert-Greifendorff and other historical figures?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Max Eckert-Greifendorff was born in Chemnitz.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2989_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Max Eckert-Greifendorff have any notable accomplishments?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2989_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do we know anything about Max Eckert-Greifendorff's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2989_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Max Eckert-Greifendorff's profession?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2989_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2989_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2989_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2989_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2989_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2989_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2989_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2989_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2989_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2989_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2989_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the document with file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2989/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt contains information about Gertrud Caspari, but not Max Eckert-Greifendorff. The other documents also do not contain any information about the birth of Max Eckert-Greifendorff in Chemnitz."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not provide any information about Max Eckert-Greifendorff's birthplace. The only relevant information is that Max Eckert (without Greifendorff) was born on 1996, but no specific location is mentioned. Therefore, the statement that Max Eckert-Greifendorff was born in Chemnitz cannot be confirmed based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There are multiple entries about individuals named Max Eckert and G\u00fcnter Z\u00f6ller, Gertrud Caspari, Matthias Seutter and Peter Herrmann who were all born in Chemnitz.  This suggests a possible bias or error in the provided information.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information about a person named Max Eckert-Greifendorff, the only mention of \"Max Eckert\" does not include a last name.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information does not provide any birthplace details for Max Eckert other than stating his date of birth as 1996, and there is no mention of Chemnitz as his place of birth.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}